[
  {
    "category": "Know Your History",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What year was the first AWS re:Invent held?",
        "answer": 2012,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What Amazon-favorite sport was introduced to re:Invent attendees in 2016?",
        "answer": "Broomball",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What world record was set at the 2017 re:Invent Tatonka Challenge?",
        "answer": "Largest chicken wing eating contest: 214 people",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "wing eating contest",
          "largest wing eating contest",
          "biggest wing eating contest",
          "largest chicken wing eating contest",
          "biggest chicken wing eating contest",
          "wing eating competition",
          "largest wing eating competition",
          "biggest wing eating competition",
          "largest chicken wing eating competition",
          "biggest chicken wing eating competition"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What year were both Lambda and ECS (Elastic Container Service) announced at re:Invent?",
        "answer": 2014,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "The Main Event",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 5,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What webinar helps people learn about re:Invent leading up to the big event?",
        "answer": "How to re:Invent",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "how to reinvent"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "How many venues does the re:Invent campus span this year (2019)?",
        "answer": 6,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What year did twitch.tv/aws start streaming at re:Invent?",
        "answer": 2016,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "How many chalk talks are scheduled for re:Invent 2019 (as of Nov 17)?",
        "answer": 694,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Let's Get Musical",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 9,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What genre of music is usually played at the re:Play party?",
        "answer": "EDM",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "electronica",
          "DJ",
          "electronic dance music",
          "electronic music",
          "house music",
          "house"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What kind of musical group kicks off Midnight Madness?",
        "answer": "Marching Band",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "marching bands"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What venue hosted the re:Play party in 2017?",
        "answer": "The Linq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "the link",
          "linq",
          "link"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Who was the re:Play DJ at the 2013 re:Invent?",
        "answer": "DeadMau5",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "deadmau5",
          "Joel Thomas Zimmerman",
          "Joel Zimmerman",
          "dead mouse",
          "deadmouse",
          "deadmous"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "People, Places, and Things",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 13,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "Who delivers the Thursday morning re:Invent keynote?",
        "answer": "Werner Vogels",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "Werner"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What sports star made a surprise experience at Midnight Madness in 2017?",
        "answer": "Shaq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "Shaquille O'Neal",
          "DJ Shaquille O'Neal",
          "DJ Diesel",
          "Diesel",
          "DJ Shaq"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What restaurant is located in both the Venetian and the Palazzo?",
        "answer": "Grand Lux Cafe",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What AWS speaker keynoted \"Tuesday Night Live\" in 2016?",
        "answer": "James Hamilton",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
